{
  "Quest 1": {
    "question": "There are many places around Ara to have lunch. Find the Student lounge and see how many microwaves there are?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "3"
  },
  "Quest 2": {
    "question": "Locate the gym inside the Whareora and find out how much it is per month?",
    "options": [
      "$10",
      "$20",
      "$40",
      "$50"
    ],
    "answer": "$40"
  },
  "Quest 3": {
    "question": "Head inside the Rakaia Centre and locate Academic Records. What documents can you get from there?",
    "options": [
      "Enrolment forms",
      "Accademic transcripts",
      "Course outlines",
      "ID cards"
    ],
    "answer": "Accademic transcripts"
  },
  "Quest 4": {
    "question": "Find the library and see how many floors it has?",
    "options": [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "4"
    ],
    "answer": "2"
  },
  "Quest 5": {
    "question": "Locate the Security office and find the after hours emergency number?",
    "options": [
      "022 123 4567",
      "022 234 5678",
      "022 345 6789",
      "022 456 7890"
    ],
    "answer": "022 234 5678"
  },
  "Quest 6": {
    "question": "Lets head outside and find the ICT helpdesk. What do they help with?",
    "options": [
      "Course advice",
      "Lost and found",
      "Library books",
      "Computer issues"
    ],
    "answer": "Computer issues"
  },
  "Quest 7": {
    "question": "Have a look round and find the tallest building on campus. lets ride the lift to the top floor. How many floors does it have?",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "8"
    ],
    "answer": "6"
  },
  "Quest 8": {
    "question": "There are two cafes on campus. Find the one that is run by staff and students. What is it called?",
    "options": [
      "one seven cafe",
      "The pantry",
      "Black Betties cafe",
      "C4 cafe"
    ],
    "answer": "The pantry"
  },
  "Quest 9": {
    "question": "There are many places to park and lock up your bike. Find the bike shed under S block. How do you get in?",
    "options": [
      "With a code",
      "With a key",
      "using your student ID",
      "It's always open"
    ],
    "answer": "using your student ID"
  },
  "Quest 10": {
    "question": "Sandy is the computing course coordinator, go and find her office.\nWhat time dose she finish on Friday?",
    "options": [
      "2pm",
      "3pm",
      "4pm",
      "5pm"
    ],
    "answer": "3pm"
  },
  "Quest 11": {
    "question": "Congratulations you have completed the quest.",
    "options": [],
    "answer": ""
  }
}